{
  "level": 2,
  "unit": 5,
  "spelling": [
    {
      "week": "1",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "The girls rode their bikes up a _____________ of dirt.",
          "answer": "mound"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I see a fluffy white _____________ in the sky.",
          "answer": "cloud"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We clap and _____________ when our team scores.",
          "answer": "shout"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Mom bought a _____________ of apples.",
          "answer": "pound"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Look at that funny _____________ on the tiny bike!",
          "answer": "clown"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Do you like the _____________ or blue shirt better?",
          "answer": "brown"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The princess wore a gold _____________ on her head.",
          "answer": "crown"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "At night a wolf will _____________ at the moon.",
          "answer": "howl"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Lin heard a dog _____________ behind the fence.",
          "answer": "growl"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "It’s nice to sit in the soft _____________ .",
          "answer": "chair"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ did Kelly put her math book?",
          "answer": "Where"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I have _____________ reading a good book.",
          "answer": "been"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I put the puzzle together by _____________ .",
          "answer": "myself"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Mateo _____________ the shopping cart through the store.",
          "answer": "pushed"
        },
        { "prompt": "Did you hear that _____________ ?", "answer": "sound" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "2",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "I planted a flower in the _____________ .",
          "answer": "soil"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To cook the fish, _____________ it in the oven.",
          "answer": "broil"
        },
        { "prompt": "The sponge feels _____________ .", "answer": "moist" },
        {
          "prompt": "Will you _____________ to the correct answer?",
          "answer": "point"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "He will _____________ for hours to plant the garden.",
          "answer": "toil"
        },
        { "prompt": "We need _____________ for the car.", "answer": "oil" },
        {
          "prompt": "Did you get a new _____________ for your birthday?",
          "answer": "toy"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "It is a _____________ to play with my dog.",
          "answer": "joy"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "What can I buy with this _____________ ?",
          "answer": "coin"
        },
        { "prompt": "Do you hear the _____________ ?", "answer": "noise" },
        {
          "prompt": "The queen wears a _____________ on her head.",
          "answer": "crown"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "There is a _____________ of dirt in the yard.",
          "answer": "mound"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ stay at your house for dinner.",
          "answer": "I'll"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I heard you _____________ at the joke.",
          "answer": "laugh"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ we can play again tomorrow.",
          "answer": "Maybe"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "3",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "This _____________ has blue walls.", "answer": "room" },
        {
          "prompt": "She is sick in bed with the _____________ .",
          "answer": "flu"
        },
        { "prompt": "Pat’s birthday is in _____________ .", "answer": "June" },
        { "prompt": "May I see your _____________ toy?", "answer": "new" },
        {
          "prompt": "We use _____________ to stick the papers together.",
          "answer": "glue"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "What is your favorite _____________ ?",
          "answer": "fruit"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ took money from the bank.",
          "answer": "crook"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I _____________ help Dad wash the car.",
          "answer": "could"
        },
        { "prompt": "This box is _____________ of books.", "answer": "full" },
        { "prompt": "Please _____________ me on the swing.", "answer": "push" },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ to each word as you read it.",
          "answer": "point"
        },
        { "prompt": "This _____________ is a dime.", "answer": "coin" },
        {
          "prompt": "The boys walk _____________ the path.",
          "answer": "along"
        },
        { "prompt": "Will it _____________ stop raining?", "answer": "ever" },
        {
          "prompt": "Jess is _____________ enough to lift the chair.",
          "answer": "strong"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "4",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "Jared kicked the _____________ down the field.",
          "answer": "ball"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A cherry is _____________, but a watermelon is big.",
          "answer": "small"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I taught my dog to shake my hand with her _____________ .",
          "answer": "paw"
        },
        { "prompt": "A shark has a strong _____________ .", "answer": "jaw" },
        { "prompt": "Please _____________ and listen.", "answer": "pause" },
        {
          "prompt": "Sam likes _____________ on his spaghetti.",
          "answer": "sauce"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Dad _____________ me how to build a birdhouse.",
          "answer": "taught"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Wes wrote his name with blue _____________ .",
          "answer": "chalk"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "How long does it take to _____________ one mile?",
          "answer": "walk"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The explorers _____________ a new place to live.",
          "answer": "sought"
        },
        { "prompt": "Is your lunchbox _____________ ?", "answer": "new" },
        {
          "prompt": "What is your favorite _____________ ?",
          "answer": "fruit"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We saw tall skyscrapers in the _____________ .",
          "answer": "city"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "No one should _____________ a wild animal!",
          "answer": "own"
        },
        { "prompt": "I borrowed a book to _____________ .", "answer": "read" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "My plant is dead because I forgot to water it.",
          "answer": "dead"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Kat biked _____________ of the others.",
          "answer": "ahead"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The _____________ weight is very heavy.",
          "answer": "lead"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Use _____________ to stitch the cloth.",
          "answer": "thread"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Do you like to eat whole wheat _____________ ?",
          "answer": "bread"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I had trouble catching my _____________ after the race.",
          "answer": "breath"
        },
        { "prompt": "_____________ the flower gently.", "answer": "Touch" },
        {
          "prompt": "Sometimes my little sister makes _____________ .",
          "answer": "trouble"
        },
        { "prompt": "Do we have _____________ class today?", "answer": "gym" },
        { "prompt": "We read a Greek _____________ .", "answer": "myth" },
        { "prompt": "The kitten is so _____________ !", "answer": "small" },
        {
          "prompt": "Use _____________ to write on the board.",
          "answer": "chalk"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "May I have milk _____________ of juice?",
          "answer": "instead"
        },
        { "prompt": "I read a _____________ book today!", "answer": "whole" },
        {
          "prompt": "What _____________ did you learn to spell?",
          "answer": "words"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
